digitaldjpool.com 2017-10-03

# The DJ Pool privacy policy

The Digital DJ Pool (“ **Digital DJ Pool** ”, “ **We** ”, “ **Us** ”, “ **Our** ”) is an online music subscription service (“ **Service** ”, as defined in the Terms and Conditions). Through our website, https://digitaldjpool.com (the “ **Site** ”), members, visitors and contributors may be requested to provide certain personal information. The purpose of this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) is to inform you about the information we collect, how we use and share that information, and the ways in which you can manage and control the use of your information. Digital DJ Pool respects your privacy.

Any personal information you provide on the Site remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions (“ **Terms** ”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you do not agree with the terms of the Privacy Policy, then please cease the registration process and discontinue your use Site immediately.

## 1\. Information We Receive or Collect from You

The information that we collect about you while you are using the Site falls into the following general categories:

### 1.1 Registration Data

When you register, we ask you to provide certain information, which includes your email address, username and password for your account (the “ **Registration Data** ”). We may also collect information you voluntarily add to your profile, such as your profile picture, hometown, biography, resume, label information, deejaying background and usernames for other social media accounts.

### 1.2 Payment Information

If you choose to subscribe to fee-based portions of the Service, you will be asked to provide your name, email address, payment information and zip code. Such information will be provided by you directly to the third party merchant site, PayPal or Braintree. You may be subject to the privacy policy of such site. The Digital DJ Pool does not have access to your payment information.

### 1.3 Information You Choose to Provide to Digital DJ Pool

When you use the Service, we automatically collect certain information, including, without limitation: (i) information about your type of subscription; (ii) your interactions with the Service, including with songs, music crates, other Digital DJ Pool users, and advertisements which are offered, linked to or made available on the Site; (iii) the details of the queries you make; (iv) User Content (as defined in the Terms); and (v) any emails you may send through the Site.

### 1.4 Listening and Downloading Activity

When you use the Service, we keep track of your listening and downloading activity, which may include the number and title of songs you have listened to or downloaded, the songs that you flag, like (thumb up), or dislike (thumb down), and the crates you create.

### 1.5 Community Posting

You have the ability to post comments on songs and to post information in community networking features accessible through the Service, such as your public profile.

### 1.6 Log Data

DJ Digital Pool may collect certain non-personally identifiable technical information through the use of log files and servers. Information in a log file may include your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount spent on particular pages, Internet service provider, date/time stamps, MAC address, and other usage information and statistics.

For clarity, to be considered personally identifiable, there must be enough information that allows others to recognize you. Please note that just because you can identify yourself, it does not mean you are uniquely identifiable to others.

### 1.7 Location Information

As part of registration for the Service, you agree to provide us with and allow us to use your zip or postal code.

## 2\. How We Use Information We Receive or Collect

We may use the information we collect, including your personal information, to: (i) provide, personalize, and improve your experience with the Service; (ii) ensure technical functioning of the Service, develop new services, and analyze your use of the Service, including your interaction on the Site; (iii) communicate with you for Service-related purposes, including promotional emails or messages; (iv) enable and promote the Service, including features and content of the Service, such as sharing, user interactions, notifications and suggestions, and integration with third party services; (v) enforce this Privacy Policy, the Terms; and (vi) as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.

## 3\. How We Share Information We Receive or Collect with Others

We may share the information we collect, including your personal information, as follows:

### 3.1 User Content

Any personal information, images, audio content or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on your profile page, via messages, comments or otherwise) or allow us to record and disclose (in messages or otherwise) becomes publicly available and can be collected, seen and used by others besides us. The Digital DJ Pool cannot be and is not responsible for any unauthorized third party use of such information.

### 3.2 Email Address 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. If you would like to change your email settings or opt-out of receiving emails, you may do so by logging into your account and changing your settings under the “Settings” tab.

If you send us emails, you should be aware that information disclosed in emails may not be secure or encrypted and thus may be available to others. We suggest that you exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal or confidential information in emails. We will use your email address to respond directly to your questions or comments.

### 3.3 Service Providers and Others

We may contract or partner with third parties to provide specialized services on our behalf, such as credit card processors, customer support, advertisement servers, and bulk email processors. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to Digital DJ Pool. They are not authorized to use your personal information for their own, unrelated purposes. Third party service providers’ processing of user data will typically be subject to security and confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

### 3.4 Other Sharing

In addition to the above, we may also share your information to third parties to (i) allow a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets; (ii) to respond to legal process, if we have good faith belief that it is necessary to do so; to comply with requirements of mandatory applicable law; to protect the safety of any person; to protect the rights and property of Digital DJ Pool, including to enforce the Terms; and to address fraud, security or technical issues; and (iii) to inform business partners about the use of the Service.

## 4\. How We Secure Your Information

We use commercially reasonable and generally-accepted technological safeguards to secure any information we collect about you. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Thus, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit through the Site. It is not a guarantee that the information you provide may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our safeguards.

The Digital DJ Pool operates in the United States. As a result, your personal data will be processed by us in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you access this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of any and all information you provide to us in the United States.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, you may log into the Site and cancel your account in the “Billing” tab. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## 5\. Your Preferences

Through your account settings, you can choose which communications you receive from us and manage your public profile information. However, this may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Site because such information may be required in order for you to register for Membership; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our Site.

## 6\. Conflict Resolution

We are committed to resolving disputes as soon as feasible and shall endeavor to resolve all disputes brought to our attention at https://digitaldjpool.com/contact in a prompt manner in accordance with the Terms. Digital DJ Pool reserves the right to make the final determination of whether a violation of its privacy guidelines has occurred.

## 7\. Policy Changes

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. Your use of the Site after any such change will be deemed acceptance of such changes. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Should you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please email us at https://digitaldjpool.com/contact.
